Pick up. Come on,pick up.
接电话 快点接电话啊
Hey,it's me.
嘿 是我
We need to talk.
我们该谈谈
I can explain everything.
我可以解释
Call me.
回我电话
No!
不要!
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- 隆重呈献 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=- Sync: YTET- 邦德猪
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译:藉秋风 老辣菜 小懒猫  猫爷 校对: 猫大爷 时间轴: 邦德猪
NCIS Season 11Episode10
海军罪案调查处 第十一季 第10集
Then there's your medical history...
这是你的病历
the LI-90 for life insurance, the DA-93...
LI-90是人身保险 DA-93是...
You're lucky this is just a temp Joint Duty assignment.
你该庆幸这只是临时合作任务
Just a few forms left.
还剩几张表了
Like the Notification of Personnel Action,
人事部的通知单
the TA-44 and the background questionnaire for your new security clearance.
TA-44和背景调查问卷 是在你的保密协议里的
- Roda. - Bishop's gonna be useless for the next week.
- Roda - Bishop这周可不好过
Should we rescue her?
要帮她吗?
No.
不
If she can't handle Roda, Gibbs is gonna melt her brain.
要是她连Roda都搞不定 那她绝对招架不住Gibbs
Oh! And I'm gonna need...the DD-817 ASAP.
还有 尽快给我DD-817文件
Oh,this is actually version 6045.
这是6045版本吧
The DoD is up to v49 on the DD-817.
国防部的DD-817表格 已经升级到49版本了
Black pen only,no smudges.
黑笔填写 不准涂改
And don't test me...
别想考验我
kitty-cat.
小屁孩
I can see you, gentlemen.
我看得见你们 先生们
What just happened?
发生什么了?
Did I do something wrong?
我做错什么了?
No,you just passed your first test.
不 你刚过了第一关
Roda,from HR--legendary.
Roda可是人力资源的传奇
But don't get too cocky.
但也别骄傲自满
Still got to take that polygraph.
你还得去做测谎
I have to take another polygraph?
还要来一次测谎?
And then all you have to do is survive Special Agent Leroy Jethro Gibbs.
然后你只要能过 Leroy Jethro Gibbs那一关就好了
- In case you haven't heard,the man is... - He's actually coming up behind you right now.
- 你知不知道他是个... - 他现在就在后面朝你们走过来了
You're not supposed to do that.
你别说出来啊
What did I do now?
我做了什么?
You've made a friend.
你交了个朋友
Grab your gear.Got a dead Marine in Potomac Heights.
抄家伙 在波托马克高地发现了海军尸体
You waiting on something,Bishop?
还在等什么 Bishop?
I don't have any gear.
我没有家伙
Good. You can drive.
很好 那你来开车
Okay.
好的
Corporal Ron Flegman,
Ron Flegman 下士
23,stationed out of Quantico,worked in the motor pool.
23岁 驻扎在匡提科 在车辆调配场工作
He live here alone?
他一个人住吗?
Upstairs.Already spoke with his CO.
住楼上 和他指挥官谈过了
Solid Marine, stellar evaluations.
是个可靠的海军 有很高的评价
Not much else.
没别的了
Well,if this was a mugging,it was a really bad one.
如果是路劫的话 也太低劣了
We got a witness.
我们找到个目击者
He saw someone enter the back of the building just prior to the shooting.
他看见就在枪击前 有人进了大楼的后门
We even got a sketch, courtesy of Magic Fingers here.
我们甚至花了个素描 来自这位神笔马良
Here you go.
看
That's a clown.
这是个小丑
Well,uh,a street performer,yes.
是个街头表演者
See,there weren't very many details,
因为没有太多的细节
so I used Jumpy,from Jumpy's Funhouse,as a template.
所以我就用了Jumpy游乐园里的 Jumpy做样板
Jumpy had this really big,like,this,like,red nose, and when he smiled,
Jumpy有个又大又红的鼻子 然后笑的时候
he... It was this kids show I used to watch,when I was little.
这是个我小时候一直看的儿童秀
Um,we were told there were several street performers who work the area.
我们得知有几个街头表演者 在这一带演出
With any luck,maybe Jumpy the Clown had a permit.
也许小丑Jumpy正好有执照
Check the licensing office.
询问下发证部门
Pull every permit on the block.
把所有郊区的执照调出来
Nice.
好样的
Oh,thank heavens we're indoors.
感谢老天我们在室内
It's been a brutal week.
这周太冷了
And I have a chill I just can't shake.
冷气直入骨髓
Me too. Anybody mind if I do some jumping jacks?
我也是啊 不介意我做些原地弹跳吧?
- Yes.
- 介意
Well,preliminary cause of death appears to be two gunshot wounds to the chest.
初步断定胸口的两枪造成了死亡
Yeah. From medium range.
是的 一般射程
Ah,Ms. Bishop.
Bishop小姐
Would you care to take a closer look at the wound?
愿不愿意凑近点看下伤口?
sure.
当然了
Yeah.
好的
Note this one.
记下来
It's oval in shape,
椭圆形的形状
which means that the bullet penetrated the skin at an angle.
说明子弹成角度穿透皮肤
Huh. Can you get a trajectory from that?
能从中得出弹道吗?
Well,possible trajectory,yeah.
很有可能啊
Very astute.
很聪明啊
Also,we get a core temperature,we can approximate time of death.
还要测个尸温 来推测大概的死亡时间
Boss,he's got a second cell phone.
老大 他还有个手机
Anything on it?
上面有什么吗?
Well,it's password-locked,
有密码锁着
but looks like he received almost a dozen missed calls just prior to the shooting.
不过在枪击前有好几个未接电话
Maybe somebody was trying to warn him.
也许有人想警告他
I know that number.
我知道这个号码
Adams House hotel.
亚当酒店的
Doesn't your dad always stay there?
你父亲不是经常待在那里吗?
Yes,but...
是的 但是...
no,no,no.
不 不 不
He's at a skin peel retreat,300 miles away, so there's no way.
他在300英里远的地方静修呢 不可能的
You know,checkout's in half an hour.
还有半小时就退房了
Whoever called our victim might still be there.
不管是谁打给受害者 可能还在那里
McGee,you got the crime scene.
McGee 你保护现场
DiNozzo,with me.
DiNozzo跟我来
that... that was...
这也太...
that was fast.
迅速了吧
- Fast. - Yeah.
- 可不是 - 是啊
Manager said the calls came from room 103.
经理说电话是从103房打出来的
Registered to Mr. Smith.
登记人是Smith先生
I'm gonna go with "alias"" what do you think?
我觉得是化名 你说呢?
Manager coming to open it up?
经理来给我们开门吗?
No.She gave me the key.
不 她把钥匙给我了
Since it's two minutes after checkout,technically,we have a right to enter.
反正都退房两分钟了 我们有权进去
That's funny, that looks like your ex-wife.
好奇怪啊 好像你前妻啊
Champagne first,and then...
先来杯香槟 然后
a little...
再来点...
Well,tie me up and call me Loretta.
捆绑我 叫我小甜甜
Wowzers.
老天啊
This is not what it looks like.
事情不是这样的
Right. We were just...
是啊 我们刚刚其实...
No,I do not need the details.
不 我不需要细节
I wouldn't mind a few details.
我不介意听细节啊
- Okay,look... - Zip it,windbag. Not another word.
- 好吧 听着 - 闭嘴 话痨子 不准再说了
What are you talking about? The cat is out of the bag.
你在说什么呢? 事情已经败露了
It just sort of happened,okay?
只是就这么发生了而已
We were gonna tell you. We just kept it hush-hush because...
我们本来想告诉你的 她结婚了
She's married.
所以我们比较低调
Because we're concerned that Emily won't take it well.
因为考虑到Emily不一定能接受
She's 13,this can be...
她才13岁 可能不能理解
confusing. And Victor and I are separated,we're getting a divorce.
还有Victor和我正在分居 我们准备离婚
Your turn. What the hell are you doing in our room?
该你了 你们在我们房间里做什么?
Well,we got a dead Marine.
有个海军死了
His cell phone got a call from this room just prior to his murder.
就在案发前 他的手机 接到了这个房间的电话
That's impossible.
不可能
We've been in this room since last night,and I haven't used the phone.
我们昨天晚上开始就一直在房里 我没有用过电话
Oh,but I'm getting a feeling she has.
但我觉得她用了
Diane...?
Diane?
Could I speak with you?
能和你谈谈吗?
Privately?
私底下?
- If you'd like to be shot. - Okay,fine.I used the phone.
- 要是你愿意被枪击的话 - 好吧 我用了电话
But not to call some Marine.
但是不是打给海军的
I was trying to call my boyfriend Eddie.
我想打给我的男朋友Eddie
Oh,that's funny. It sounded like you said boyfriend.
真滑稽 你刚说男朋友?
Well,ex-boyfriend,now. I was calling to break it off.
前男友 我想打电话去分手的
While I was in the bathtub?
趁我在洗澡的时候?
You had a boyfriend while I was in the bathtub?
趁我洗澡的时候 你交了个男朋友?
But he never picked up.
但是他没接电话
So,you don't know Private Ron Flegman?
所以你不认识Ron Flegman下士?
It's probably her fianc茅e. This is unbelievable.
有可能是她的未婚夫呢 太不可置信了
No,I've never heard that name in my life.
不 我听都没听过这名字
No,you know what?You need to calm down.
你知道吗 你先冷静下
You just said it yourself; this just sort of happened.
你也说了啊 就这么发生了嘛
So,yes,fine, you caught me.
好吧 被你抓个现行
I was dating someone else.
我是在和别人约会
But,you know,it was a little,innocent overlap.
不过是时间上有小小重合罢了
Any idea why our victim would have your boyfriend's cell phone?
知道受害人为什么会有 你男朋友的手机吗?
Ex-boyfriend,and no.
是前男友 我不知道
But,you know,I gotta say,
但是不得不说
I'm not that surprised that Eddie is mixed up with some dead guy, because,um,
我一点都不奇怪Eddie和死人搭上边
I mean,huh,he was,he was fun.
因为 虽然他是很有趣
- I don't need the details. - But the,yeah,there was,something wasn't right.
- 我不需要细节 - 但是有些事情不太对劲
I kept catching him in these lies and...
我发现他在说谎
he has no credit history.
也没有信用史
- Everybody has a credit history. - Well,that's enough for me.
- 每个人都有信用史的 - 够了
Let's go arrest him.
去把他抓起来吧
Oh,no. We're gonna talk to him first.
不 我们要先和他谈谈
I knew you were gonna say that.
就知道你会这么说
Crime scene's locked up.
犯罪现场被封锁了
Thought I'd come by and se...
所以我就过来看看
Hi,Chucky.
嘿 帅哥
What?
怎么了?
So,Agent Fornell was married to Gibbs's ex-wife?
所以 Fornell探员 和Gibbs的前妻结婚了?
Yup.
对
And the owner of the second cell phone from our crime scene was dating Gibbs's ex-wife?
而犯罪现场第二个手机的主人 在和Gibbs的前妻约会?
Yup.
对
That's quite a coincidence.
这也太巧了吧
I know. It really is.
我知道 可不是吗
You know, it's hard to imagine the same woman liking Fornell and this Eddie guy.
很难想象喜欢一个女人 会同时喜欢Fornell和Eddie
Although,maybe Diane liked him because he's not Fornell.
有可能Diane喜欢他 是因为他不像Fornell
Best leave the psychoanalysis to Ducky.
心理分析还是留给Ducky吧
If you value breathing.
要是你还想活命的话
Bishop,you could have warned me.
Bishop 你怎么不提醒我
You said I wasn't supposed to do that.
你不是叫我不要提醒吗
Tobias.
Tobias
What are you doing here?
你在这干嘛?
Just thought you might need some help.
想你可能需要帮忙
Diane's really worried, I just want to put her mind at ease.
Diane担心死了 我只是想安慰下她
Yeah,uh-huh.
是啊
You shot me in the caboose.You owe me.
你上次打中了我的屁股 你欠我的
McGee.Go.
McGee 开始吧
Okay.
好的
Uh,meet Eddie Macklin.
这是Eddie Macklin
Diane Sterling's... boyfriend.
Diane Sterling的男朋友
Ex-boyfriend.
前男友
He's 31 years old and works at a local climbing gym.
31岁 在当地的一家攀登健身房工作
Yeah,and...?
还有呢?
And that's it, we couldn't find anything prior to six months ago.
就这么多 六个月之前的东西我们都查不到
No parking ticket, library card or bus pass.
没有停车证 图书卡或者公交卡
Interesting.
有趣了
Let's go ask him about it.
我们去问他不就得了
God...
老天
Yeah,I knew him.
是的 我认识他
He came in about six months ago, looking for a job.
他六个月前来这里 说要找份工作
He teaches our Basic Climb class.
他教我们的基础攀登课程
His chest is bigger than Diane's.
他的胸部比Diane还大
You know where he is?
你知道他在哪里吗?
No. And he actually blew off a private lesson this morning.
不知道 他早上旷了节私人教练课
But I don't think Eddie was a big fan of the student.
我认为Eddie不是很受学员欢迎
How about this guy?You know him?
这家伙呢? 认识吗?
Yeah,that's him.
嗯 就是他
That's Eddie's student.
Eddie的学员
Geez,what happened?
天哪 怎么回事?
Corporal Flegman was shot.
Flegman下士被枪杀了
We found Eddie's cell phone on him.
我们在Eddie身上找到他的手机
We'd like to talk to him about it.Among other things.
我们想和他谈谈这事儿 还有其他的
I knew Eddie was trouble.
我知道Eddie有麻烦
Just something off about him.
他有点不对劲
You know where we can find him?
你知道哪里能找到他么?
I don't know-- his apartment?
我不知道 他家里?
Uh,it's empty.
额 家里没人
No car registration with the DMV.
机动车驾驶管理处没有租车记录
That's weird. He has a car.
这就奇怪了 他有辆车
I got the info on his employment application.
他就职申请表上有写
- Let me get it. - Thanks.
- 我去拿过来 - 谢谢
Yeah,suspect's vehicle is an '88 silver Lincoln Town Car.it's a DC plate.
是的 嫌犯的车是辆88年的银色林肯房车 华盛顿牌照
Have Bishop run the BOLO.
让Bishop发布全境通告
- You sure? - Yeah.
- 你确定? - 是的
On it.
马上
Grab a bite?
要不要去吃点东西?
I'm good.
我不饿
Beer?
啤酒?
Long day,Tobias.
今天累了 Tobias
What the hell am I doing,Gibbs?
我在搞什么啊 Gibbs?
I feel like I've been swallowed by a python,cut my way out and then crawled back inside again.
我感觉像被头巨蟒吞了 好不容易杀出条血路 然后又自己爬回去
- Sounds about right. - Oh,come on.
- 说的很对 - 噢 拜托
Are we making a mistake?
我们做错了么?
- ** - ***
- Tobias - 什么
What are you looking for?
你想要什么?
Not just sex,if that's what you're getting at.
不只是性 如果你要问这个的话
- Stop. - But don't get me wrong,no,
- 打住 - 别误会我
- it's better than... - Just stop.
- 总好过... - 打住
I'm just saying that there's something different this time.
我想说这次有不一样的感觉
Maybe because we're exes.
可能因为有前任的关系在
You should try it. I mean...
你也去试试 我是说...
with another one of your ex-wives,
找你另外的前妻试
not this one,'cause this one's... taken.
不要找这个 这个已经有主了
Can I go home now?
我现在能回家了吗?
You are the worse advice giver I've ever met!
你是我见过的最糟糕的建议者!
Don't quit your day job.
千万要保住你白天的工作
I think...
我觉得...
as long as you're happy, that's all that matters.
只要你开心 就足够了
Happy?
开心?
What's that got to do with anything?
怎么扯到开心上去了?
It's my neighbor.
邻居打来的
She watches Emily.
她帮忙照看Emily
What'd she do now?
她这回又做了什么?
No,I'll go.
不 我去
She didn't come home for dinner again.
她又没回家吃晚饭
Third time this week.
这周第三次了
I've got to go prowl the mall looking for her.
我得去商场里巡逻堵她
Rain check?
改日再约?
I can wait.
我等的住
No way in hell am I living with either of them,if they're back together.
假如他们复合 我才不要和他们住一起
Can I stay one more night at your house,Uncle Gibbs?
我能在你家再住一晚吗 Gibbs叔叔?
We can watch African Queen again.
我们再看一遍非洲皇后嘛
Your parents want you back.
你爹妈要你回去
They didn't want me back last night.
他们昨晚就没要我回去
I'm 13-- they'd let me emigrate to Jupiter if I could get a ride.
我13岁了 要是能搭上车 我移民到木星都没问题
Morning. I entered Eddie Macklin's vehicle information into the NCIC database,
早上好 我把Eddie Macklin的 车辆信息输到了NCTC数据库
along with a physical description.
外加他的外形描述
Then I sent out copies to all law enforcement agencies.
然后给所有执法机构发送了复印件
- And then I-I just felt like... - Bishop.
- 然后我觉得... - Bishop
You can just say "BOLO's out."
你只用说 全境通稿已发
BOLO's out.
全境通稿已发
He actually told me you're doing great,
他告诉我你很不错
but you need to relax a little.
但是需要放松点
Can't say I disagree.
真的哦 要放松
- Emily. - Thank you.
- Emily - 谢谢
Do you have any idea what kind of trouble you are in,missy?
小姐 你知道自己惹了什么麻烦吗?
Me?!
我?!
You're the one who's ruining your life.
是你在自毁生活好伐
I beg your pardon?
你说什么?
Uh,www.you-and-dad-suck- together.com?
额 www.你和老爸重归于好.com?
Or are you too desperate at this point to care?
或者你已经疯到没考虑那么多了?
Apple doesn't fall far from the tree,huh?
有其母必有其女 是吧?
How dare you talk to me like that.
你怎么敢这样跟我说话
You and Dad speak to each other?All you guys do is fight.
你和老爸会讲话? 你们只会吵架
We do not fight.
我们没有吵架
We are just very loud!
只是说话声音比较大
Best let them wear each other out before I get into it.
但愿我被扯进去之前 她们已经筋疲力尽
Right. And you!How could you do this to me?
好吧 还有你! 你怎么能这么对我?
Honey,no one is doing anything to you.
宝贝 没人对你怎么样
Your mother and I are just...
你妈妈和我只是...
Wait a second.
等等
How exactly do you know about...
你是怎么知道...
your mother and me?
你妈妈和我?
I know everything.
我什么都知道
I put a keystroke logger on both your Facebook accounts.
我在你们俩facebook上安了击键记录器
- You what?! - You need a warrant to do that!
- 你什么?! - 要有法庭许可才能安那玩意儿!
Gibbs,Gibbs,Gibbs,Gibbs,Gibbs,Gibbs.
Gibbs Gibbs Gibbs Gibbs Gibbs Gibbs
I cracked the suspect's cell phone.
我破解了嫌犯的手机
There are boatloads of juicy texts on there from him to Fornell's ex-wife.
有一大堆他发给Fornell前妻的暧昧短信
I mean,this stuff is-is kinkier than Fifty Shades of Grey.
比还露骨 (畅销的情色小说)
You have got to come see this...
你赶快去看看...
Fornell.
Fornell
Ex-wife.
前妻
Daughter.
女儿
You get back here or I will smash
你给我回来 否则我就把 实验室的所有电脑都砸碎
every computer in that lab! Don't you touch my babies!
不许碰我的宝贝!
Can I apply for asylum?
我能申请收容所吗?
Abbs,I hope you told Gibbs to come alone
Abbs 希望你叫Gibbs单独过来
'cause Fornell's head would explode if he saw these texts.
要是Fornell看到这些短信 肯定会气到脑袋爆掉
- Better get a mop. - Tony! If you value your life,
- 你最好准备个拖把 - Tony! 如果你爱惜自己的生命
you will turn off that computer right now!
马上关掉电脑
Touch that CPU and I touch you.
敢碰下CPU 我就对你不客气
I can't hear you.I have a sinus infection.I have to go get my neti pot.
我什么都听不见 我有鼻窦炎 我要去找洗鼻壶了
No,no. Oh...
不 不 噢...
Hey,what happened?
嘿 怎么回事?
I'm prepared for any contingency.
以防万一准备的
You are interfering in an ongoing investigation.
你这是妨碍正在调查的案子
Turn that computer back on.
给我把电脑开起来
Okay,Tobias,I sent most of those texts before you and I were back together again,
好吧 Tobias 这些短信 是你和我和好之前发的
so... they're inadmissible.
所以...这些不能用来定罪
Okay. Just show me the texts that Mata Hari here sent after we got our game on.
好吧 那就把我和这位玛塔哈里在一起后 发的短信给我看(荷兰舞女 传奇女间谍）
Let's see how innocent that innocent overlap really was.
我们来看看那段小小的 重合期到底有多小
- Everybody still alive? - Yes,just wounded.
- 大家都还活着吗? - 还活着 受伤了
- By betrayal. - Where's Emily?
- 因为背叛 - Emily在哪儿?
Conference room with Bishop. And she's fine.
和Bishop在会议室 她很好
You got anything besides Diane's texts?
除了Diane的短信 还有其他的吗?
Yeah.
有
The suspect,um,sent a few texts of his own.
嫌犯另外发了几条短信
He mentioned a safety deposit box at a local bank.
短信里提到一家银行的保险箱
- Who'd he send them to? - A burn phone with a black market number.
- 短信发给谁的? - 一次性手机 黑市买的号码
So something is definitely afoot here.
这里头肯定有猫腻
You got the name of the bank?
哪家银行?
Let's go check it out.
一起去看看
Slow down.
慢点
I want Diane to come along so she can I.D. her ex-boyfriend from the security tapes.
我想让Diane一起去 以便从监控录像里指认她前男友
So?
然后?
So I'm not bringing both of you.
我可不想把你们两个都带去
The locksmith is almost finished with the safe deposit box.
锁匠差不多打开保险柜了
Let me go check on the security footage.
我去看下监控录像
Would you like something to drink?
要喝点什么吗?
No,I'm good.
不用
I'll take a water. One straw,two pieces of ice, three slices of lemon.
来杯水 一根吸管 2块冰 3片柠檬
Jethro,what the hell am I doing?
Jethro 我到底在搞什么啊?
I feel like I drove into a ditch,towed my car out and then drove right back in again.
感觉我开车进了臭水沟 好不容易爬出来 又径直开了进去
Oh,God,please don't make me do this.
噢 上帝啊 救救我吧
This is all your fault.
这都是你的错
What? If you hadn't shot Tobias in the ass,I wouldn't have had to nurse him back to health.
什么? 要不是你开枪打了Tobias的屁股 我就不用照顾他到康复
He was so vulnerable.
他当时很脆弱
You know,his pride was so wounded and...
他的自尊心受伤了 然后...
Then one night I was helping him with his bath...
然后有天我帮他洗澡...
Stop. Stop.
打住 打住
What is wrong with you two?
你们俩怎么了?
I just need to know if you think we're making a mistake.
我想知道 你觉得我们是不是在犯错...
It depends. Uh...
要看情况 呃...
What are you... looking for?
你想...要什么?
I just want to...
我只想...
wake up next to someone I love.
早上醒来 身边躺着我爱的人
Here's Mr. Macklin's safe deposit box and the security footage.
这个是Macklin先生的保险柜和监控记录
Thank you.
谢谢
He rented the box a month ago.
他一个月前租的箱子
There's been a lot of activity since then.
那之后活动很频繁
Define "a lot."
有多频繁
He's been here over ten times in the last three weeks alone.
过去3周 他来了10次以上
Well,who stores stationery in a safe deposit box?
谁会把信纸藏到保险柜里?
Perhaps he removed the important contents on his last visit.
也许他最后一次过来 把重要的东西都取走了
Let's see his last visit.
看看他上次的录像
Oh,that's Eddie right there He doesn't appear to be carrying anything.
噢 那个就是Eddie 手里好像没拿东西
Who the hell is she?
她是谁?
Looks like a girlfriend.
看起来像是女朋友
Girlfriend?
女朋友?
While we were dating?
我们约会期间?
That two-timing
该死的劈腿狂
- son of a... - Hey. Diane.
- 狗娘... - 嘿 Diane
While you were dating Eddie,you and Fornell were...
你和Eddie约会时 你和Fornell...
Oh... forget it.
噢...别提了
Did she have to sign in,too?
她有登记进入么?
No,just the box's owner.
没有 只有保险箱主人签字
Well,we're gonna have to find her.
我们得找到她
We will. Relax.
我们会的 放松
She's our only lead to Eddie.
她是我们找到Eddie的唯一线索
The bullet fragment bounced around the acetabulum, flew up to the iliac crest...
子弹碎片弹到髋臼 飞到髂嵴
Before exiting just below the coccyx. I'm telling you,Doctor,it's amazing.
然后从尾骨下面穿出去 跟你说哪 医生 这太神奇了
Let me guess. The JFK Magic Bullet Theory?
让我猜猜 肯尼迪的神奇子弹理论?
Oh,ac-actually it's... Agent Fornell's heinie.
噢 实际上...这是Fornell探员的屁股
Uh,I'm sorry. Uh...
啊 我很抱歉 啊...
to what do we owe the pleasure?
很乐意为你效劳?
Ooh. Uh,pleasure,no. But,uh,
噢 乐意 噢...
I do need to better familiarize myself with...
我需要让自己熟悉下....
actual dead people.
死人
Who are dead.
死者
I thought you might be able to help me.
我觉得你能帮我
You've come to the right place.
你来对地方了
Say hello again to Corporal Ron Flegman.
和Ron Flegman下士打个招呼吧
Hello.
你好
We confirmed that the gunshots were the cause of death,
我们确定他是中枪身亡
but that is really just the start.
但这仅仅是开始...
For example, the,uh...
比如 额...
Postmortem lividity on the body indicates that the victim wasn't moved after the murder.
尸斑表明受害者死后没有被挪动过
That-that is... that is correct.
没错
Uh,however,the bruise on the front of his calf there,
他小腿肚那里的瘀伤
it indicates that...
表明他...
He was diabetic.
他是糖尿病患者
Necrobiosis lipoidica, I think it's called.
好像是叫类脂质渐进性坏死
That's also correct.
这也说对了
I took the liberty of reading the Handbook of Autopsy Practice this weekend.
这个周末我冒昧的读了 尸体解剖实践手册
The whole thing?
全部的?
It's-it's over 600 pages.
一共有600多页呢
It was 596,actually.It was really cool.
实际上 一共596页 非常酷
Happy first official joint duty BOLO to you.
庆祝你的首个 行政合作任务全境通告
It's a very special moment.
这是个非常特别的时刻
Blow out the candle. Make a wish.
吹熄蜡烛 许个愿吧
My BOLO on Eddie Macklin came in?
我关于Eddie Macklin的 全境通告有结果了?
Your wish came true.
你的愿望实现了
Ah. Airport police found his car in a long-term parking facility.
机场警方发现他的汽车 在机场的一处长期停车场里
Rock on. Let's go get it.
太棒了 我们去把它带回来吧
Mm. We are.You aren't.
嗯 我们去 你不去
You have a little appointment with the polygraph person.
你跟测谎人员有个小约会
Already?
这就要吗?
Don't worry. It's gonna be fun.Polygraphs...
别担心 会很有趣的 测谎仪...
Who doesn't love talking about themselves?
谁会不喜欢谈论自己呢?
I was dropping Emily off at school.
我把Emily送到学校了
I heard you found Diane's ex-boy-toy's car.
我听说你发现了Diane的 前男玩伴的汽车
Yeah,he left it in long-term parking at the airport.
是的 他把车停在了机场的长期停车场
What a pile of junk.
真是一堆垃圾
Hath the woman no shame?
这女人不觉得丢脸吗?
Can you believe he's half her age?
你信不信他只有 她年龄的一半?
I guess you weren't stallion enough,Chuckie.
我猜你是没那么种马 帅哥
Agent Fornell, I swear,we never...
Fornell探员 我发誓 我们绝不会...
Yeah. Diane told me the same thing,and I believed her,
是的 Diane跟我说了同样的话 而且我相信了她
though current circumstances are throwing a bit of cold water on her credibility.
虽然现在的状况已经 向她的信誉泼了一盆冷水
You run down the flights out of the airport?
你检查过机场的出港飞机了?
Yes. There's no Eddie Macklin listed.
是的 名单上没有Eddie Macklin
So why was he parked there?
那他为什么要在那里停车?
That's not the half of it.
还有更奇怪的呢
Not only did we find a clown nose in the trunk but we also found blood on...
我们不仅在后备箱里发现了 小丑的鼻子 还发现了血迹...
Abby. We're supposed to wait for Gibbs to get back.
Abby 我们应该等Gibbs回来
Oh,right. Never mind.
哦 对 就这样吧
You found blood in the car?
你在车里发现了血迹?
Minute traces of it everywhere.
到处都有微量的痕迹
We think someone tried to clean it up.
我们认为有人试图 将它擦拭干净
But I was still able to detect blood proteins from at least four separate victims.
但我仍然能从血清蛋白中判断 这至少来自四名受害者
What... You're saying that Diane's ex was some kind of serial killer?
什么 你是说Diane的前任 是某种连环杀手?
That's...
这太...
We interviewed all the street performers licensed in the area where Corporal Flegman was killed.
我们询问了Flegman下士遇害的那个 区域内所有登记的街头表演者
- They all had alibis. - And very large shoes.
- 他们都有不在场证明 - 还有超级大的鞋子
At the moment, that leaves one remaining suspect.
目前 只剩下一个嫌疑人
Diane Sterling's ex-lover,and owner of a Lincoln with multiple blood stains in it.
Diane Sterling的前情人 布满多人的血迹的林肯车的车主
What,Diane?
怎么了 Diane?
Well,have you found him yet?
你们找到他了吗?
No,we have not found him yet.
没有 我们还没找到他
It's the same answer as the last four times when you called.
跟你前四次打来电话的答案相同
We found circumstantial evidence in this car linking him to Flegman's murder,
我们在车里找到了他与 Flegman谋杀案有关的间接证据
but no indication  of his current whereabouts.
但是没有迹象表明他现在的下落
What,Tobias? Aren't you with Diane?
什么 Tobias? 你没跟Diane在一起?
Are you holding anything back?
你是不是隐瞒了什么事情?
No,I am not holding anything back.
没有 我没有隐瞒任何事情
I will tell you when I have something.
我一有消息就会告诉你
Fine.
好吧
Oh,I can't believe I was so worried about that polygraph.
真不敢相信我怎么会对 测谎这么紧张
I mean,at NSA, they ask you everything.
我是说 在国安局 他们什么都问你
As in,like,everything.
就像 所有事情
I'm surprised you guys don't have,like,more personnel issues with how...
我很惊讶你们这些人居然没有 比如 更私人的问题...
I am interrupting something.**
我好像打断了什么事情 你希望我离开吗?
No. I want you to work.
不 我希望你工作
That means we tell him what we know.
意思是我们要告诉他 我们知道的消息
Oh. So far,no luck using facial recognition to track our mystery woman.
到现在为止 我们还没能幸运的通过 面部识别系统追踪到我们的神秘女人
I'm still working on it.
我还在继续解决
And Abby hasn't gotten any hits on the blood samples we found in Eddie's car.
而Abby也没有从我们在Eddie车上 发现的血液样本中发现任何匹配结果
Total is five individuals.
一共有五个人
All right,expand the BOLO.I want this guy's photo
好的 扩大通缉范围 我希望这个家伙的照片
in every train station, in every bus station.
贴在每一个火车站 每一个汽车站
That's a bad idea.
这是个坏主意
I mean... I might have a better idea.
我是说... 我可能有个更好的主意
Look,Eddie is coming back.
听着 Eddie马上就会回来
If he was ditching his car, there are easier places to abandon it than at an airport.
如果他想要弃车 那他可以找到 比机场容易得多的丢弃地点
We should put it back and watch it,and when he comes to pick it up...
我们应该把它放回去 监视它 一旦他回来取车
We grab him.
我们把他抓起来
Absolutely not.
当然不是
We follow him, see what he does,where he goes, then we grab him.
我们跟踪他 看他做了什么 去了哪里 然后我们把他抓起来
Works for me.
我看行
I got the first shift.
我先走了
Don't tell anybody where I am.
别告诉任何人我在哪里
Why do you always go for the gun?
为什么你总是喜欢用枪?
What are you doing here?
你到这儿来干什么?
Well,don't worry, I'm not gonna stay.
别担心 我不会留下的
I know. It wasn't the question.
我知道 这不是我的问题
Tobias and I had a family dinner planned with Emily,
Tobias和我跟Emily 有一个家庭晚餐的计划
and she left us a message, saying she had other plans,
然后她给我们留了一条消息 说她有其他的计划
so I thought maybe she'd come back here.
所以我以为她可能 会回到这儿
Try the mall.
去商场找找吧
Yes,that's where I'm going right now,thank you.I will let you know.
是的 我马上就要去 谢谢你 我会告诉你结果的
I hope you and your gun have fun together.
希望你和你的枪在一起过得愉快
Can't believe she missed me.
真不相信她没抓到我
Who doesn't check the closet when they're clearing a house?
谁会在清理房间的时候 不检查壁橱?
Who doesn't turn off their cell phone when they're hiding in a closet?
谁会在躲进壁橱里的时候 不关手机?
Wasn't my cell phone.
不是我的手机
I forgot I set my Happy Cat Friend Alert Watch to let me know when the Columbo marathonstarted tonight.
我忘记我设了我的欢乐猫找朋友手表 提醒我今晚Columbo马拉松的开始时间
Have to tell your mom. She's worried.
必须跟你妈妈说一声 她很担心
I know. I know. Just give me two minutes.I need your help.
我知道 我知道 给我两分钟时间 我需要你的帮助
All right,what do you need?
好的 你需要什么?
I want you to help me convince my parents to break up.
我希望你帮我说服我的父母分手
They listen to you.
他们听你的
And you know they aren't right for each other.
你知道他们彼此不合适
You've seen them fight.
你见到过他们吵架
They fighting a lot?
他们经常吵架吗?
In public,yeah.
当着大家的面 是的
It's like they have a fetish for it.
就好像他们上了瘾似的
But... when it's just the three of us,it's not so bad,I guess.
但是 当只有我们三个人在的时候 我感觉好像不是那么糟糕
But you know this will end badly.
但是你知道这肯定会糟糕的收场的
Well,yeah,it might.
是的 可能吧
Then I get to watch them break up all over again.
所以我要当心他们又分一次手
Oh,I... I'm confused.
哦 我有点糊涂了
You-you-you don't want them together?
你 你不想让他们在一起?
Or you're scared that they're gonna break up again?
还是你担心他们 会再一次的分开?
Why would I be scared of that?It's what I want!
我为什么会担心这个? 这正是我所希望的
Uh... Wait.
等等
Now I'm confused.
现在换我糊涂了
You suck at this!
你这方面真是太烂了!
Yeah,it's Gibbs.
是的 我是Gibbs
Bishop and I are at the airport.
Bishop和我在机场
Eddie's back. He picked up his car.
Eddie回来了 他开走了他的车
We're tailing him now.
我们现在在尾随着他
Yeah,stay with it. Let me know.
好的 继续 随时告诉我情况
Will do.
遵命
Two minutes are up,kid.Let's get you home.
两分钟到了 孩子 我们去你家吧
Give me a sit-rep.
给我汇报情况
Eddie drove all night.
Eddie整夜都在开车
I think he was trying to see if he had a tail.
我想他是在设法确认是否有跟踪
He finally came here, parked his car and disappeared.
他最后来到这里 停下了车然后不见了
Fornell's covering the rear.
Fornell在断后
Okay. DiNozzo,you're with me.McGee,Bishop, you got the exit.
好的 DiNozzo 你跟着我 McGee Bishop 你们守住出口
We're clear.
没有人
Looks like Hannibal Lecter's little hobby center.
看起来像汉尼拔博士的小型爱好中心
Boss.
老大
I got this.
交给我吧
NCIS.
NCIS
Get on the ground, put your hands on your head!
跪在地上 举起手来放到头上
Where do you think you're going?
你觉得你还能去哪里?
Oh,come on.
哦 拜托
Senior FBI Agent Tobias Fornell.
FBI高级探员Tobias Fornell
I believe you know my wife.
我相信你认识我太太
Is he gonna hit me again?
他还要再打我吗?
No. And...
不 而且
And I apologize for that.We just really needed to talk to you.
而且我要向你道歉 我们真的需要跟你谈谈
Yeah,about what?
好吧 谈什么?
Aren't you gonna ask what happened?
你不打算问问发生了什么吗?
Flegman was a student of yours.
Flegman可是你的学生
What happened?
发生了什么?
You slept with my wife!
你跟我的太太上了床!
What happened... was that...
已经发生的事情是...
your student was murdered... with your cell phone on him.
你的学生被谋杀了 而你的手机在他的身上
And then you disappeared.
然后你失踪了
Why is your car covered with blood?
为什么你的汽车上布满血迹?
And what's with that little shop of horrors we found you in?
我们找到你所在的那个小型 恐怖商店是做什么的?
Oh,that storage unit-- that ain't mine,bro.
哦 那个小仓库 不是我的 兄弟
Oh,I suppose this isn't yours,either.
那我猜这个也不是你的了?
We found 20 more of those hidden in the storage unit.
我们发现了二十多卷 都藏着小仓库里
That's almost 100 grand.
将近十万美元
It's a lot of cash for a gym teacher.
这对于一个健身教练来说 可是不少钱啊
I need to get out of here.
我必须离开这里
Now. If he thinks I took off with his money...
马上 如果他认为 是我拿走了他的钱...
Who?
谁?
You ain't arrested me.
你们不能逮捕我
Everything you got is circumstantial.
你们知道的一切都是间接的
So some people cut their fingers in my car.
就不能是有人在我车里 不小心切破手指吗
You got any bodies, aside from this loser who took the wrong cell phone at the gym?
除了这个在健身房里拿错了手机的傻瓜 以外 你们发现其他尸体了吗?
I know my rights,man.
我知道我的权利 哥们
You got to arrest me or let me go.
你要么逮捕我 要么放我走
What's it gonna be,fellas?
结果会是什么情况呢 小伙伴?
Yeah,that's what I thought,too.
对了 我也是这么认为的
Whoa,hold on.
哦 等等
What is that?
那是什么?
Arrest it is. Our forensic tech traced the blood in your car to an unsolved quintuple homicide.
逮捕令 我们的法律技术人员将你车里的血迹 追踪至一起未解决的五重谋杀案
So,sit down, you walking midlife crisis!
所以 坐下 你要步入中年危机了
This is nuts,man! I didn't kill anybody!
这是胡说 我没有杀过任何人
That blood is ten years old!
那些血迹有十年之久了
The car's from a police impound!
是来自于警察依法扣押的财产
So how are you driving it?
所以你是怎么 能开这辆车的?
'Cause my name isn't Eddie Macklin.
因为我的名字不是Eddie Macklin
It's Special Agent Edward McKenzie.
我是Edward McKenzie特别探员
I work for the Secret Service.
我在美国特勤局工作
And you two are about to blow a highly-classified six-month op.
而你们两个马上要破坏一次 六个月之久的高度保密的行动
Our financial crimes division has been working a money-laundering case for over year.
我们的金融犯罪部门从一年多以前 就在解决一起洗钱案
We traced one of the sources of the cash to the Tower Gym.
我们追踪到其中一处 现金来源是Tower健身房
I went in undercover.
我便去做了卧底
Found out the cash came from a bank-robbery gang run by the owner,
发现现金来自于 健身房主Elijah Banner和他的女朋友
Elijah Banner, and his girlfriend.
所运行的一个银行抢劫帮派
There's our mystery woman from the bank.
这就是我们在银行 看到的神秘女人
Elijah told me to rent a safe deposit box there so she and I could case the place.
Elijah告诉我在那里租一处银行的保管箱 这样她和我就可以侦查这个地方了
Oh,were you casing her,too?
你是不是也侦查她了?
Sorry,guys.Boss,she's like a cat. When she found out...
对不起 同志们 老大 她就像猫一样 她一发现...
Hello,Diane.
你好 Diane
Oh,I heard we broke up.Sorry about that.Oh,and I'm a Secret Service agent.
哦 我听说我们分手了 很遗憾 哦 我是一名特勤局的探员
I heard. What's with the attitude?
我听说了 这是什么态度
I don't know. Maybe it's,you were sleeping...
我不知道 也许是 你在我们约会的时候...
...with your ex-husband while we were dating.
还跟你的前夫上床
Man has a point.
他说中了要点
You guys are buddies now?
你们俩现在成战友了?
Yeah. We were thinking of starting a club.
是的 我们在打算开家俱乐部
Yeah?
是吗?
Well,watch it,boys.
那小心点 少年们
I know something about each and every one of you
我知道你们每一个人 的一些绝不希望外人
that you don't want anybody else to know.And I got a Twitter account.
知道的小秘密 而且我还有推特账户哦
We need to get back to work.
我们必须开始工作了
Hey,let go of me!
嘿 放开我!
- Come on! - You take your hands off me right now!
- 过来! - 把你的手拿开!
sorry
对不起
So,how was Corporal Flegman involved?
那么 Flegman下士又是怎么牵涉进来的?
Flegman drove the getaway car,but Elijah thought he was skimming.
Flegman是负责开头车的 但是Elijah认为他想跑路
Looks like Elijah finally did something about it.
看起来Elijah最终还是行动了
Why haven't you taken this guy down?
你们为什么没有拿下这家伙?
He keeps his hands too clean.
他撇得很干净
We need to catch him in the act.
我们必须抓现行
When you picked me up,I was collecting gear for his next robbery.
你们抓我的时候 我正在为他下一次抢劫收集装备
But if Elijah thinks I took off with his money,
但如果Elijah认为我携款潜逃了
six months of work goes down the drain.
六个月的努力就付之一炬
We can get him for Flegman's murder.
我们能用Flegman的谋杀案来抓他
No way he pulled the trigger.I'm guessing it was his girlfriend.
他才不会亲自动手 我猜是他女友干的
She's the clown. Freelances at kids' parties.
她就是小丑 儿童聚会上的自由职业者
We want to get this guy, we need to put the money back,
如果我们要抓他 必须把钱放回去
and I need to get back on the street before he notices I'm gone.
而且我要马上回去 免得他察觉到我不见了
It's Elijah.
是Elijah
He's noticed.
他察觉了
I got to answer it.
我必须接
Yeah,put it on speaker.
好 开免提
Yo,E,what's the word,man?
哟 有什么吩咐 老大?
Cut the bull, I know you got pinched.
别废话 我知道你被逮住了
Put agent Fornell on the line.
让Fornell探员听电话
Agent Fornell.
我是Fornell
You got something of mine. I got something of yours.
你拿了我的东西 我也拿了点你的东西
Dad,I'm in a white van, no windows,I can smell pine...
爸爸 我在辆白色的房车里 没有窗户 有松木的味道...
You ever want to see your daughter again,you give me back my money.
你想要再见到你女儿 就把钱还给我
I'll be in touch.
我会再联系你的
I said everybody, every asset we have.
我们必须用上所有人和所有资源
He's got my daughter, for God's sake.
他抓的可是我的女儿
We found a camera hidden in the storage locker.
我们发现储物柜外有个隐藏摄像头
Must be how Elijah knew we had his money.
Elijah一定是这样得知钱的事
He watched us collect the evidence.
他看到我们在收集证据
We need to be ready when he calls.
他打来的时候我们必须有所准备
I have friends standing by to help trace the callback.
我有朋友随时准备好追踪电话
Right. His apartment's been cleaned out,he's running.
好 他的公寓已经空了 他跑路了
Any word on the BOLO?
全境通告有什么消息?
Police are stopping every windowless white van they see.
警察正在盘查每一辆 没有窗户的白色房车
Your daughter was very brave.
你女儿非常勇敢
They found a broken window in the kitchen.He was in our house.
他们发现厨房的窗口破了 他来过我们家
It's gonna be, it's okay,babe.
会好的 会没事的 宝贝
Okay. It's okay.
会没事的
Emily's gonna be all right.
Emily会回来的
DiNozzo,what do you got?
DiNozzo 有什么发现?
Elijah's girlfriend is dead.
Elijah的女友死了
Looks like he's tying up loose ends.
看起来他正在斩草除根
You got any idea where he's going?
你知道他会去哪里吗?
Well,no,
不知道
but he's not improvising.We found surveillance photos of Fornell and Emily.
但他可不会即兴发挥 我们找到他监视Fornell和Emily的照片
Elijah probably started making exit plans the moment you two showed up at his studio.
在我俩出现在他工作室的那一刻 Elijah也许就开始准备后路了
Zeroed in on your daughter as a lever he could pull.
你的女儿就是他最好的砝码
Blocked call.
隐藏号码
Tony,keep us posted.
Tony 随时报告
Will do.
遵命
Agent Fornell.
Fornell探员
I just texted you my location.
我刚刚发给你我的位置
I want you to send that girl.
我要你叫那个妞
The one who helped you clear out my storage locker.
那个帮你清空我的储物柜的妞来
She's got eight minutes to bring me
她只有8分钟的时间
my money,by herself.
只许她一个来
Once I'm safely away,I'll tell you where you daughter is.
一旦我安全离开 我会告知你女儿在哪
She's fine. But if you even think of sending anyone else, I'll know.
他没事 但如果你企图派其他人来 我会知道的
And your daughter will pay the price.
你的女儿会付出代价
Okay.
好的
Okay,but just so we're on the same page:
但这样 我们的立场都是一样的
if so much as touch a hair on my daughter's head,so help me God,I will find you.
如果你敢动我女儿一根汗毛 上天入地我也会找到你
and I will rip your eyes out of your face and shove them so far down your throat
我会把你的眼珠挖出来 从你的喉咙一路塞进去
you'll need a proctologist to read the evening paper.
直到你得用你的菊花来看路为止
He hung up.
他挂了
What's the move,boss?
下一步怎么办 老大?
No,this is your call,Tobias.
你来决定 Tobias
Bishop,you're the analyst.
Bishop 你是分析师
Is he gonna let my daughter go if we give him his money?
如果我还钱给他 他会让我女儿回来吗?
Yes. He's demonstrated...
会 他表现出...
I've got it.
知道了
I just need to know if you are up for this.
我只想知道你准备好没有
Yes.
好了
Then we give him his money. Gibbs?
那我们就把钱还给他 Gibbs?
No tricks.
不耍花招
You can catch him later.
你们能晚点再抓他
We just want our daughter back.
我们只想让女儿平安回来
Comm check.
通讯检查
Yeah,we read you.
收到了
How you doing,Bishop?
你怎么样 Bishop?
I'm fine,surprisingly.
感觉很好 出乎意料
Tell Agent Fornell I can do this.
告诉Fornell探员我应付得来
He's in the conference room with Diane,but,will do.
他跟Diane在会议室 会转告的
Okay,so...
好 所以...
I guess I just sit somewhere and wait?
我猜我该坐下来等?
No,keep moving.
不 继续走
Avoid a static blind spot.
避免成为静止的盲点
Remember,this guy's a killer.You don't want him sneaking up on you.
记住 这人是个杀手 你不会想让他偷偷跟上你的
Okay,less fine now.
好吧 感觉不那么好了
Wait,I see something.
等等 我看到了
There's a jogger approaching.
有个慢跑的接近了
Right build.
身型符合
It's him,no white van.
是他 看不到白色房车
All right.
很好
- Dump the cash  in here. - Okay.
- 把钱倒进去 - 好的
Where's Emily?
Emily呢?
- Take this. - Okay.
- 拿着 - 好
- Wait here.
- 在这儿等着
When I'm clear,I'll call you with Emily's location.
我安全离开以后 我会打给你告知Emily的地点的
That was the deal.
这是我的条件
Okay.
好的
It's done.
结束了
I've lost sight of him.
我看不见他了
But he gave me a cell phone,said he was gonna call with Emily's location.
但他给了我一台手机 说会告诉我Emily的位置
Any way to find out where that cell's been?
能有方法查出 这台手机曾经到过哪里吗?
We can run its IMEI number.
我们可以查手机的身份码
Right. If we find out where it's been,we might be able to figure out where he's going.
对 如果我们找到它曾经的位置 我们也许能找到他去过哪里
Yeah,do it.
好 马上查
Okay,uh,it'll just take a minute.
马上就好
Aah,what was that noise?
这是什么杂声?
I don't know.
我不知道
Give me a sit-rep.
快向我报告
Okay.
好
Okay,this doesn't make any sense.
这完全说不通
There's no upside to killing her.
杀了她对他没有任何好处
He's made all the right moves,so far.
他目前的行动都是有利的
So what's the play?
到底这次在玩什么花样?
He can't use the white van to get away--Emily's description made sure of that.
Emily的描述让他不能 再开那辆白色房车逃跑了
Bishop,report.
Bishop 报告
Okay,he doesn't want to risk calling.
他不打算冒险给我打电话
But he has to know if Emily isn't found ASAP,he's looking at an AMBER Alert.
但他知道如果Emily没有及时被找到 安珀警报就会发出
Then he'll never get away.
那他就逃不掉了
So,how does she get found?
所以 应该怎样找到她?
He painted the van.
他重漆了房车
Damn it.
该死
Wait,wait, wait,wait,wait!
等等 等等 等等!
You okay?
你没事吧?
Okay,you're okay.
没事了 没事了
You're okay. I'm gonna get you out of here,okay?
没事了 我这就把你救出去
Hang on.
撑住
Dad..Mom.
爸爸...妈妈
I'm so glad you're all right.
你没事太好了
I love you.
我爱你
I was so worried about you.
我担心死了
Nice work.
干得好
- Thanks. - Yeah.
- 谢谢 - 嗯
Next time you take your earwig out of your ear,
下次你再把耳机摘下来
Bishop...
Bishop...
I'm gonna use a staple gun.
我就用订书机钉上
Yeah,uh,I was worried if the Fornells found out about the cell phone...
呃 我担心如果Fornell一家发现手机...
Yeah. Yeah,I know.
是 我知道
Like I said...
就像我说的...
Nice work.
干得漂亮
Thanks.
谢谢
I need another hug.
我要再抱你一次
- I am so proud of you,baby. - Oh,I am,too.
- 我以你为荣 宝贝 - 我也是
I'm fine. He didn't hurt me.
我没事 他没伤害我
I was just so worried about you guys-- are-are you okay?
我倒是挺担心你们俩 你们还好吧?
Oh,yeah,we're... Oh,oh,yeah.
哦 是 我们...呃 是
We're just so happy that we're all together again.
我们只是很高兴又能在一起了
And we-we're just so glad that-that you're safe and you're back.
我们也很高兴你毫发无损地回来了
Hey,any word?
有什么消息?
Nothing. No sign at the airports or train station.
没有 机场和火车站都没有消息
McGee's talking to Highway Patrol, but I got a sinking feeling he got away.
McGee跟高速公路警察谈过 但是我感觉他已经逃之夭夭了
Oh, he didn't get away.
哦 他才没有逃之夭夭
My last name is Fornell,after all.
怎么说 我也是Fornell家的人
Freeze.
不许动
You're under arrest.
你被捕了
No. Move...
你敢动...
so I can shoot you.
我就开枪
I'm not carrying a cell.
我身上没有手机
This bike's untraceable. How'd you find me?
这摩托是追踪不了的 你们怎么找到我的?
We didn't.
不是我们
My daughter did.
是我女儿
Say hello...
来打个招呼
to her Happy Cat "Friend Alert" watch.
这是她的欢乐猫"找朋友"手表
It's Bluetooth enabled.
带蓝牙功能
It beeps any time a friend wearing the same watch gets within 30 feet.
30英尺范围内出现 另外一只手表的话就会响
Course,I had to boost the range on the second watch to track you,but...
当然 我得把另一只手表的 探测范围扩大来追踪你...
That little bitch.
小贱人
Watch your mouth.
嘴巴干净点
I'd hate to get suspended,and Agent Gibbs already has enough paperwork.
我可不想被停职 而且Gibbs探员手头的文书工作已经够多了
I should have never let her go.
我应该干掉她的
I'm sorry,Gibbs.
抱歉了 Gibbs
It's okay.
没事了
Eh,told you he'd run.
看 告诉你他会拔腿就跑
Come on.
别这样
We just came to say thank you.
我们只是来感谢你的
You already said thank you.
你们已经谢过了
This time we brought liquor.
这次我们带来了酒
Well,then,you're welcome.
那 不用谢
And...
然后...
And we have a request.
然后我们有个请求
Oh,I can't wait.
哦 等不及了
Oh,will you stop with your whining?I mean,you're a grown man.It-it's,it's unattractive.
能别发牢骚了吗?你是个成年人了 这 这真让人讨厌
What are you doing?
你在干嘛?
We're here to ask a favor and you're insulting the man.
我们是来求他的不是来骂他的
He has been carrying on like he lost his dolly.
他一直表现得像个丢了糖的小孩
He hasn't said five words since he's got here.
我们到这里以后 他说的话还没超过五个字
Anyway,we'll be out of your hair in a minute.
随便了 我们很快就打扰完了
It's just...
就是...
Well,uh,you've probably noticed that...
呃 你大概注意到了...
Tobias and I--
Tobias和我...
clearly gluttons for punishment--
都因太贪心而受到了惩罚...
are trying to make a second go of things.
现在打算再做一次努力
And,uh,we...
所以呃...
We,um...
我们 呃...
We...
我们...
Oh,for Pete's sake.
哦 真要命
We want your blessing.
我们希望得到你的祝福
My what?
我的啥?
Your blessing.
你的祝福
It's very important to Diane.
这对Diane来说很重要
And me.
对我也是
That we have your blessing.
能得到你的祝福
Why?
为啥?
Because it-it...
因为 这 这...
What is with the 50 questions,do we have it or not?
问那么多问题干嘛 你到底祝福不祝福?
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- 隆重呈献 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=- Sync: YTET- boss家长不好当啊!笑死
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译:藉秋风 老辣菜 小懒猫 猫爷 校对: 猫大爷 时间轴: YTET- boss家长不好当啊!笑死